people see the cars the Bugattis Jets
the G4S the Richard Mills the trips but
it wasn't always like this 2019 I was
actually in depth I was in depth about
$30,000 for all the money that I had
saved up in Dunkin' donuts and money
that I had borrowed from my family and I
lost everything I literally lost
everything that I had saved and asked
for for people to trust in me in 3
months trying to enter a New Journey and
even with that I entered this very deep
I don't want to say the depression but
very frustrated phase in my life where I
pretty much lost connection and contact
with everybody in my family because not
only did I lose all their money but I
was doing the complete opposite they
said so it all started in the middle of
2018 um working at Dunkin Donuts making
8 $9 an hour where I'm probably be
making $15 to $1,800 a month that's
working the 40 hours a week showing up
every single day and as I'm working here
for more than 6 months I'm realizing
this is not the life that I want to live
this is a very un happy lifestyle I I'm
feeling the pattern of literally waking
up working clocking out going home
eating sleeping repeating literally
every single day but there is one thing
that I do remember from that time that
completely changed everything for me I
was actually in a rush on my way to go
clock in early in the morning because I
had the morning shift the Dunkin' Donuts
I had to make the bagels I had to make
the donuts I had to make the waffles I
had to make the coffee everything had to
happen very early and I ran a red light
and there's a camera on this red light
that automatically sends you a ticket to
the house I didn't even know and uh I
got my paycheck that same Friday in the
mail cuz I would get everything to my
house and then I would just direct
deposit it into my bank account and I'll
never forget I get one mail that has my
Dunkin Donuts check and then I have
another mail that is a ticket from the
red light when I looked at the amount of
each ticket they're both identical my
paycheck for that week was $158 cuz I
missed two days cuz I felt like I was
sick or something and then the ticket
for running the red light was
$158 this is where my mind completely
went ballistic I'm like I just worked a
whole entire week to pay a red light
ticket that I got trying to rush to get
to my job this is where I completely
changed my whole entire mindset and my
ambition on who I want to be and I knew
that working that 9 to5 that 7 to6 7 to
4 was not going to be it and you know
what thanks to that red light ticket
that is where it all started that is
where I realized this is the new
beginning of me trying to figure out how
I'm going to be successful how I have no
idea but I know there's other people out
there that are successful why can't I so
I did what every young 18-year-old would
do go on the internet search up how to
make money online and you got many
different options that would pop up and
I was one of those guys that I was very
skeptical of these people making money
online the guys that would pop up on the
ads my first initial thought is scam
this guy's trying to take my money and
the product that he's selling doesn't
work it's not real he just makes money
from selling products and I was in
complete denial but I kind of ran into a
dead end every single time I was trying
to learn a new journey I needed to get
educated I had to learn how to do what I
wanted to do I just wasn't going to go
to the Super Market and find somebody
that did it cuz I didn't know who does
what so the easiest way is just either
watching videos and trying to figure
figure it out or get educated on so I
said you know what let me just take the
leap of faith and what's the worst that
can happen lose money at the end of the
day I was losing more time working a job
that wasn't making me enough money to do
anything so I said let's do it so I
started off trying to learn how to trade
stocks and that was actually the
shortest Journey because as I'm about a
week or two into it I realized that the
minimum deposit that you had to have to
be able to trade stocks was 25,000 and
at that time I did not have 25,000 so I
said okay cool on to the next this is
not for me I came across Amazon Drop
Shipping I think it is or FBA or
whatever that's called which is
basically where you resell products on
Amazon and I knew a buddy of mine that
was actually doing it and he was doing
it for about 4 to 6 months and he was
not successful at all he was very
frustrated not having any type of
results and he was maxed out on his
credit card it was kind of explaining to
me that you need to have credit limits
so you can buy things and then you sell
them and I did not have any credit cards
at that time I I didn't have anything I
didn't have money to put up that was
enough to actually start making some
type of profit with these stores but I
did a little bit of due diligence just
to understand how it works and see if
there was a way around it there
definitely wasn't and then I came across
what I thought was going to be the
jackpot Airbnb this is when Airbnb is
popping off and gr Cardone did an
interview with this guy named Brian
Paige and in the interview he's
explaining that oh you can actually own
properties cash flow them and not have
to have any mortgage you don't have to
have any down payment you don't have to
maintenance you do anything I'm like H
what's this guy talking about and it was
rental Arbitrage so he he sold me on it
I can't even lie sold me on the product
100% you basically go up to a a landlord
and say hey you want me to suas your
property myself and then I messed it up
for a whole year and give it back to you
or do you want me to do rental Arbitrage
where you lease it to me and then I sub
lease it to people every single week
people come in for a week I take a
deposit basically before they leave I
clean the house so the house has to be
in high maintenance so these new people
that are going to come in through Airbnb
rented out and then the property cash
flows so the story in the narrative was
positive for the landlord basically I
have to take care of your property so I
can continue to make money with my
business and then you're happy because
I'm paying your rent and I'm taking care
of your property and I I thought this
was really going to be it I invested
into it I got educated and uh ran into a
bunch of walls it is not that easy the
story does sound nice but I ran into a
lot of issues signing leases Lor
allowing it short-term rental zonings I
basically lost about 8 months and a lot
of money hiring people trying to figure
out these things and keep in mind I
don't know how to do any of this stuff I
just basically saw this guy on YouTube
and tried to figure it out on my own
hired clean ladies hired contractors and
I didn't know how to do any of this
stuff so it was definitely a interesting
part of the journey in my life but just
didn't work out at all so when I got
sold the dream I decided to go Allin I
get one of my buddies of mine George I'm
like dude we have to just put in all the
time into this we started you know
literally cold knocking on people's
doors started investing into like
realtor cards wearing up to people like
a for realtors we started to sign leases
and little did we know that we were
signing leases and in the areas we were
signing leases they don't allow
short-term rentals so now we have a
contract for at least for a year that we
could cancel but then we lose the
deposit it was a very frustrating 8
months that I literally made no money I
did everything voluntary hours and it
actually cost me a lot of money but you
know what there was Lessons Learned and
I realized that everything that was sold
and the picture that was painted not
what wasn't exactly as easy as it is so
after my friend pretty much quitting on
me he literally said hey look bro this
is not going to work out I can't
continue to help you on this because I
just don't see a future in it I was kind
of left by myself and by myself I didn't
want to take on all this responsibility
so I kind of had to throw in the towel
and waste all that time that's where I
entered this this very frustrated point
because I'm trying to make it I really
want to be successful and I'm I'm going
out there and I'm putting in the work
but I'm not getting anything in return
and my friend that I thought was going
to be there with me the whole time he
basically bailed on me so I'm just there
by myself about a month and a half later
I see one of my friends in college at
that time I was in my first couple of
months of college he's like hey dude you
should come to this events where they're
going to teach us how to make $250 a day
trading and I told them bro you need
minimum 25,000 I already did my research
he's like no no no no this is different
this is foreign exchange there's this
company called IM markets live they're
going to teach you how to trade live
you're going to make $250 a day so on
and so forth I'm like oh okay sure how
much is it like no dude it's free it's
an event you're going to be with other
people it's going to be great I'm like
okay whatever doesn't cost me anything I
know this guy have nothing to do I work
go to school I have plenty of free time
I go to this event and obviously I get
sold into the whole multi-level
marketing pay the subscription
and I was obviously mad at the beginning
because I got sold a dream there as well
thinking that this multi-level marketing
business was going to teach me how to
trade which they didn't but what they
did do was open the door to the
opportunity of Foreign Exchange trading
trading Forks like you can actually
trade currencies and you can start with
as little as $100 and with leverage you
are able to make a lot more money so the
entry barrier is a lot lower meaning
that I can trade because I don't have
$25,000 compared to trading in the stock
market and I started to go deeper and
deeper into the business I'm like oh
wait this is an actual gold mic you can
have 1 to 500 leverage 1 to 1,000 1 to
3,000 leverage meaning that with $1 you
have the buying power of $3,000 I
thought I was about to get rich next
week so I started putting in hours every
single day I completely left the
multi-level marketing business model
that they had and I just went straight
into the charts 10 hours every single
day 7 days a week I was locked in for a
period of 5 months where the only thing
I did was just charts and this is the
same point where my professor came up to
me in English class I'll never forget
this I'm falling asleep in the class and
he came up to me he's like hey look uh
just letting you know that you can
pretty much Ace every single test from
here to the end and you will still fail
this class so you can follow or you can
leave but you don't have to come back
because you're going to fail this
semester cuz you're just too too behind
I wasn't doing my homework wasn't
passing test and I told him I'm like
thank you very much much bro left the
class never went back in and all this
kind of happened at that same exact time
so I'm lying to my parents saying I'm
going to school I'm still working at
Duncan not making money and now I'm
trying to figure out how to make money
trading Forex when I have no idea how to
trade Forex and little did I know that
this journey of trading Forex was about
to be the most darkest and brutal
Journey that I could have ever
anticipated for it to be I entered a
rabbit hole so deep I put myself so deep
into this that I had either getting out
or dying there was no other option I was
so much into depth all the little bit of
money that I had saved up from my job I
put into it I asked my parents for
telling them that it was going to be for
financial weight and for books and I put
it into trading all of it blown I got a
total sum of about 28 $29,000 that I
blew in literally 3 months of me getting
into this journey of trading and I can't
go and tell my parents that I lost the
money they gave me for school trading I
have Cuban parents that they don't even
know how to use use a computer they
would kick me out of the house to disown
me at this point I had either an option
to succeed or I was doomed and my family
ended up finding out that I stopped
going to college they found out that I
lost all the money and they found out
how I lost it and that wasn't a nice
conversation telling my parents that I
haven't been going to school and I've
been trying to figure out how to make
money online and make back this depth of
$30,000 it it really wasn't a good
conversation to have but at that very
point I looked at myself in the mirror
and I said dude you've pretty much tried
everything out there you definitely
don't want to continue to stay out the
job there's other people in this Niche
that are successful what do they have
different than yel nothing they're all
human at the end of the day the only
thing they have ahead of me is time they
put more time into this craft than I
have I'm about a year into this journey
and I've done nothing but lose they have
eight years in front of me and they do
nothing but win well maybe I just have
to put more time into it that's that's
exactly what I did I put my head down
every single day 10 hours a day looking
at looking at nothing other than the
charts what ended up happening after
another year went by I was no longer
losing now I was at the point where I
was predicting the markets but I wasn't
making any money at first I was
literally looking at the markets and not
knowing what the hell was going to
happen now I'm looking at the markets
and I'm having not only a great bias of
if it's going to go up or down but I'm
actually predicting it to a precise
price point by exactly what day is going
to get there now all the two years of
pain are becoming actually worth it and
I came across funding companies that
they'll fund you you could buy a
challenge for a small fee if you pass a
challenge they fund you and this is
where I had basically my big crack I
like to call it the Golden Era because
things just went from not zero I was at
negative it went from negative to plus
100 in the matter of 6 months at 2 and
1/2 year mark I received my first
profitable amount of money that I got
from the market $28,000 I'll never
forget not only that I pay back the dept
that I had with my parents it's great I
get emotional and everything them
because one month just outdid 2 years of
pain and made everything worth it for me
I paid back the depth of my parents and
I said you know what let's make this
real I went I bought a Rolex for $5,000
and I bought a brand new Mercedes S550
two more months went by I had another
great growing of the account I scaled up
to $80,000 in my bank account I'll never
forget $80,000 where I had literally
never made that type of money I had left
Dunkin Donuts and my only focus was
trading but then I entered a slope that
I was not prepared for a very slippery
slope that almost cracked me completely
and put me right back in the position
that I was the same month that I quit
Dunkin Donuts and I had made $80,000 in
my account I blew $330,000 of my network
which is nearly 50% of it in one single
month I feel like I was the king of the
world I thought that I was invincible
and I felt like as if I could have won
every single trait what had happened is
that I entered a winning streak for 3
months I caught a great movement in the
market and I capitalized off of it very
well was perfectly timed but then when
that volatility started to go down I was
blinded I thought that that volatility
was going to happen forever and that I
know that me losing those $30,000 of my
net worth put me in a position where now
I'm scared to risk more money because I
don't want to go back to work I don't I
can't ask my parents for money again now
I've raised my life to a certain
standard that now I have to stay there
and continue to grow there's no way I
can go down so I pretty much cornered
myself into a position where I was full
of fear I was scared to take the next
step because I didn't want to lose I
didn't want to continue in pain but I
said you know what if I made it this far
and I made this much money by simply
showing up every single day what did I
do wrong so I started analyzing my
mistakes I go back and I look at my
trade history and I started looking at
the trades that I took the losses on and
I started to look at the trades that I
took a win on that's where I realized
that I was taking a good amount of
Trades that were trading with the trend
when I won and when I was taking trades
that I would lost I was taking trades
against the trend so there I see a
little bit of a pattern then I realized
that when I was making a lot of money I
was trading less when I started losing
money I was trading more
and then I realized how much I was
risking whenever I would risk less I'd
make more whenever I would risk more I
would lose less these three things
combine is probably one of the most
powerful data points that I could have
self-analyzed in my whole entire Journey
because what that did it just not only
made me redefine everything I was doing
wrong and helped me optimize what I was
doing right but now I was no longer
scared to take a Next Step because I
knew exactly now why I failed and I
fixed it and I double down on what I did
right and that combined gave me a new
updated trading plan but there was one
thing that I
realized I wasn't holding my trades long
enough I wasn't capitalizing off of the
markets that I was predicting and that's
where sudden forget was born I was
scared of cutting my profit short I was
scared of letting the trade hit my stop
loss I was even scared of holding that's
where set and forget literally played in
the factor perfectly set and forget took
my results to a completely different
level not only that I analyze my losses
and fix them but now I optimize my wins
like I have never done before I was
making so much money by simply set and
forgetting that I didn't even know what
to do with it the same exact trades that
I was taking where I was making 500 to
1,000 now I'm making 2 3 4 $5,000 why
because I'm set and forgetting I'm
making 10,000 a day $2,000 a day even
$30,000 in one single day because I am
holding and maximizing the winning
trades that I was catch it and all this
thanks to this one day I'll never forget
I was trading London session meaning I
had to stay up very late into the night
and early into the morning I'm obviously
very tired cuz I haven't slept all night
and I have a lay down chair where I
would just either lay back take a quick
nap or just lay down and get comfortable
just to watch the trade cuz I'm watching
the markets for 10 hours a day and this
one day I fell asleep on the chair and I
fell asleep in the chair with about
$4,000 in profit and I never placed to
take profit numbers because again I
wanted to maximize my profits I would
just actively monitor it and close it
myself I fell asleep in the chair I Wake
Up 3 hours later from a very Hefty nap
and I'm up
$115,000 I was making money in my sleep
this is where everything now made sense
maximize your profits and cut your
losses set of [__] forget and that
very day this set and forget strategy
not only changed my life but it started
creating this massive Colts all around
the world because it's something that
Traders all around the world were
struggling on take entering a trade and
just set un forgetting it is as simple
as that then you fast forward to two
years applying the set and forget
strategy and I had officially now become
a millionaire Trader meaning I have a
million dollars in the bank account a
million dollars in my trading account
and this felt good but this was only the
tip of the iceberg I was only getting
started in the ability that I had and me
realizing the potential that this Market
had out there for me a million dollar in
trading is nothing and the more money I
started to see it it wasn't it wasn't
enough I wanted more I wanted to go from
Seven figures to eight figures but the
type of person that you have to become
to go from a seven figure to eight fig
Trader you have to enter a whole new
dark journey and I wasn't ready for that
I wasn't ready to see $200,000 in the
loss and then swings of $500,000 in
profit and then another $200,000 in the
loss and again I know I know that's all
percentages at the end of the day but
it's my first time entering this type of
Swings with high numbers that I had
personally never seen before on a
personal account but nonetheless the set
and forget strategy didn't fail me I was
following the same exact trades the only
difference is that now I'm risking a lot
more than I was originally risking I was
risking on my personal account anywhere
from 2 to 5% but now I'm risking 10 15
20% because I want to be an eight figure
Trader and I know that there's risk
behind that I just have to be ready to
to accept it at the beginning I wasn't
and I took more losses than I should
have and I beat myself up for it but I
believed in my strategy and I believed
in myself to not only get out of those
losses but come out on top and end up as
an eight figure Trader that I am now
today where I have made more than $13
million using this set and forget
strategy but even then when I got to
this level I got bored like really like
now what am I going to go from an8
figure Trader to a nine fig Trader I
actually didn't want that I didn't need
more money I have more money than I know
what to do with what I need is a purpose
I needed something to keep me motivated
make me want to wake up in the morning
and actually go trade stay up at night
something that makes my brain churn
something that challenges me I'm a
competitor at heart and I want to win it
and I feel like I beat the game when you
beat the game in GTA you don't ever go
back and play it until you're done
that's what I felt like so what I
decided to do is create a new mission
that is to turn $100 into a million this
that you see here in the matter of 2
months I'm going to turn it into this or
even this or even this now little did I
know this mission was going to [__]
be long I thought I was going to be
doing it in 1 month cuz I'm the best
trainer in the world it took me over a
year to complete the 100 to the mill
series took me to the bottom where I
even took a break from social media I
took me five six different attempts
where I was up
$300,000 and then I ended up blowing it
in one single week it's it took me 3
months to make it up to $300,000 in the
account and gone like this in one single
week and all of this done publicly in
front of every other Guru in the
industry in front of you guys documented
on Instagram telegram Discord YouTube
everywhere I'm literally showcasing this
journey that I went to when I took the
100 to 300K and when I lost the 300K in
front of everybody it's a bit
humiliating it hurt my reputation and a
little bit of my ego because nobody
wants to lose hundreds of thousands of
dollars in front of everybody but you
know what I have a challenge that I need
to complete and I wasn't going to let
that stop me I wasn't going to let that
loss Define who I am the way I come back
from that loss defines who I am and we
gave the 100 to the mil challenge
another go but this time it was even
more legendary because not only did we
complete the 100 to the mill challenge
finally after a year of doing it we did
it live in front of hundreds of
thousands Traders we turned on the live
stream and we did not turn it off until
the account did not end on a million
dollar this is the best way to Showcase
Traders how legit trading industry is
and the opportunity that it has to offer
for you all you need is a winning
strategy I literally took $100,000 to
1.03 million in 3 months showing the
before the during after of every single
trade documented on across every single
platform and as soon as I completed this
challenge I realized what now what what
am I going to do a million to a trillion
no I don't want to deal with those
swings H yes it is technically
percentage by the end of the day I am
human seeing multiple seven figure
swings is something that I don't want to
have to deal with right now at 24 years
old I'm very content with my life right
now I don't need to have that type of
stress on me at all but what I do like
to do is change people's lives take
people that have this opportunity in
front of them and they don't know what
to do with it because I figured this out
by myself I had this passion me I had
this dog in me and I had the opportunity
and I had to go do it by myself if I
didn't go do it for me nobody else was
and it took me 2 and 1/2 years to really
understand it and remotely see anything
now I have students where I get this
opportunity put it in front of them and
show them how to use it correctly and in
the first 6 months they have made six
figures this is what drives me now this
is for me the full circle picture
showing to the people that they're
probably skeptical that if this is legit
or not showing them opportunity and then
getting them to have results cuzz I was
that same person when I got started I
was skeptical and I needed somebody to
give me the opportunity so then I could
have results and then I actually believe
in it and that is what drives me now
that is exactly what the 30-day boot
camp is for where I'm going to be taking
a selected amount of people and taking
them from Level zero to level 100
showing them the ins and outs of the set
and forget strategy literally taking
them by the hand showing them from step
one all the way through the 100 so they
can make trading their main source of
income in this upcoming year because
comparing the six six Monon Journey from
myself and to somebody like J and juus
where in J and Juice's first 6 months
he's made six figures and myself in the
first 6 months I'm still trying to
figure out what a pip is correctly you
would have a completely different
perspective and idea of trading Forex
myself at 6 months still trying to
figure out what a pip is I don't know
how I kept going and I say 90% of the
people nowadays don't have that fire in
them to keep it going compared to Jaye
juice his first 6 months he makes
figures this guy's set for life and
that's why I want to be that person for
you be that person that I wish I had
when I got started back in 2019 and I
was trying to figure out is this trading
[__] really legit and for anybody out
there that is asking themselves is this
really legit are those real testimonials
is I even all real go watch myund to the
mil series that is the exact reason on
why I did it for people out there that a
skeptical to take this leap of faith I
took a $100 investment and I scaled it
to seven figures live in front of
everybody showing the before the during
the after and for those of you that want
to see the sum up of this whole entire
challenge where I literally took the 100
into the mill in this video right here I
show you the key highlight points that
made me actually be able to complete the
challenge there were certain points
where I had to make executive decisions
and if I didn't do it correctly I would
completely blow the account and that led
me to be able to turn $100 into a
million and I'll tell you what I could
do it all again and I hope that this
video leads you to understand that
behind the the lifestyle behind the cars
behind the success there is a journey
and people are usually jealous of the
results but nobody's jealous of the
journey so if you're in a position where
you want to get to this point be ready
for the journey thank you guys for
watching this video all the way to the
end I'll see you in the next one